[playful music playing]
[Ayame] Hey, sissy.
It seems like Chii
doesn't even want a boyfriend.
She said she's too busy with basketball.
What? Give me a break!
She's a girl in high school!
This is the age
when people fall in love with each other!
I've been on high alert
for the past few days.
And there's basically no end to the guys
who seem interested in her.
If I were her, I'd go down the line
and chat each one of them up.
Yeah, but you're not an ordinary person.
I wonder if there's someone
she's got her eye on.
Sissy, you do know you always get quiet
when my guesses are right.
- [groans softly]
- Who is it? Who is it?
Do I know this someone?
Now! I need his name, age, birthday,
and his emergency contact!
You expect me to know all that?
[Ayame] If Chii's interested in him,
then this must be some awesome guy!
Could it be...
[gasps] They got to know each other
while practicing in the gym?
Who could say...
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
I need you to spill the tea!
- Please, please, please, tell me.
- This is not good.
If she finds out about him,
she'll definitely meddle.
-Maybe I should lie to her.
- Please, sissy.
[Chinatsu] He's totally awesome!
He's my favorite player.
Spill the tea!
- C'mon, sissy!
- [sighs]
Are you listening?
The person Chii likes
is this tall, older, handsome guy.
He's a bit wild, and good at basketball.
He lives overseas in another country.
[gasps]
That sounds like a great match!
Anyone less than that
wouldn't be good enough for her.
[Karen] It's a lie.
But this is still better
than her finding out the truth, right?
[playful music ends]
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
[coach] Kazuma Matsuoka,
our second-year who was studying
in the U.S. is back with us.
Thanks. It's good to be back.
- [Ayame gasps]
- [all] Welcome back!
[Ayame] A tall handsome guy
who just came back from overseas
and is good at basketball?
That's the guy!
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 22
INOTA!
[Ayame] A tall handsome guy
who just came back from overseas
and is good at basketball.
I didn't think that kind of superhuman
actually existed,
but that guy right there
is a perfect match for her.
Chii! I'm rooting for you!
- [Taiki] Manager.
- [Ayame groans]
[upbeat music playing]
I do have a name after all,
and it's hella cute.
Ayame? Ring a bell?
Okay, then, Ayame,
you forgot to fill this part out.
What? But I double-checked it
and everything.
What the...
Was he always in basketball club?
He studied abroad for a year,
which so explains
why he's not only handsome,
but also worldly!
And rumor is
he's really good at basketball.
Isn't he the coolest?
Though, if I'm being honest,
Yusa is more my type!
Haven't you only seen the guy one time?
[footsteps]
- [Taiki] Hina.
- [Hina] Hm?
What's up?
So, did you hear?
The other day during practice,
Uchida from Volleyball Club--
Yeah, I've got the deets
on that one already.
[Ayame] It's the cute girl
from the Rhythmic Gymnastics Club.
[laughs] Old news!
[Ayame] Hm.
[Hina] Huh?
[Ayame] Well, well, well.
Something is going on there.
BURNABLE
So gross.
There's no way I can make
taking out the trash look cute.
[footsteps approaching]
[gasps softly]
- Hi there again.
- Huh? Oh, yeah, hello.
[Ayame] Excuse me, but...
Yes?
I'm asking you because
I'm manager of Badminton Club,
and this is probably
gonna come back to me somehow...
Tell me, do you have feelings for Inota?
What?
- Yes! I could sense it!
- [groans]
You were making a girly face back there,
so I was suspicious.
I so was not.
Inota's not to be underestimated, then!
Especially if a cute girl like you
is interested in him.
And don't worry,
he's not the kinda guy I go for.
You can lock him down,
Rhythmic Gymnastics.
Um, what was your name?
Hina Chono.
He's the kind of guy
who just needs a little push.
But once Inota knows how you feel,
he'll wanna date you for sure.
Oh, he already knows how I feel about him.
[Ayame] What? You confessed to him?
[Hina] Yep.
But I told him
I didn't need a response right away.
To be honest with you,
I had a feeling that he had
only been looking at me as a friend.
[Ayame] Hm.
I didn't think it would help
keeping my feelings to myself.
And I wanted him to see me
as a possible girlfriend.
Huh?
So, he still hasn't given you an answer?
Uh-huh.
Do you think it's because you said
you weren't in a hurry to get one?
Yeah, maybe.
[grunts angrily]
What's with him?
Confessing to someone takes guts, and yet,
he's making you do all the work?
Isn't he just taking advantage
of the fact that you like him?
[Hina sighs]
Chono, listen, you can't let him
be free-range anymore.
You've gotta grab him
by the neck and capture him.
Aren't you exhausted the way things are?
Not really.
It's actually fun having a crush on Taiki.
[gasps]
- That's adorable.
- [groans softly]
[Ayame] Does he not know
that there aren't many girls
who will care about him
as much as she does?
[gasps]
Okay. Leave it to me.
Your love is gonna be reciprocated.
I'm gonna help you.
Wait, really?
I'm Ayame Moriya.
An ally to girls out there
giving it their all.
Just you wait, Inota!
[gasps softly]
[whimsical music playing]
[sighs]
- Inota!
- [exclaims]
Yes?
Chinatsu, why are you
calling me that now, too?
I just thought it was a good nickname.
Don't call me that.
I think it's kinda embarrassing.
Oh, really?
Well, you wouldn't like it
if I called you "Chii," would you?
INOMATA
- Actually...
- Huh?
I wouldn't mind...
if you were to call me Chii.
[gasps softly]
Ha. Not.
What?
- [door slides]
- [Chinatsu] I'm home.
[Taiki] Once again,
I don't know where we stand.
Welcome home. Oh, did you
buy something while you were out?
This is...
a secret.
[sighs]
Is this too much? Or too little?
DON'T OVERWATER.
WILL FLOWER WITH SUNLIGHT.
[sighs]
You said it's called "Fall Camp?"
Yup, yup.
It's four whole days.
It's always on a long weekend
this time of year.
This year, we're all excited
'cause it's gonna be a joint training camp
with the basketball
and rhythmic gymnastics clubs.
[boy 1] And the lodgings there
are pretty nice, too.
But the practice drills are absolute hell.
[exclaims]
GRIN
Oh! That sounds great.
Everybody staying in one place?
It's gonna be fun!
Since the basketball team
is going to be staying with us...
it'll be a chance for Chii and fab-hair
to get to know each other better.
[grunts]
[sighs]
Leave it to me.
[grunts]
This is our chance to get
Inota and Hina-bean together!
[Hina] Hm?
[Ayame] I mean, if a girl
as cute as Hina-bean confesses to you,
you'd be out of your mind not to date her.
- [shuttlecock thudding]
- Mm?
[grunts]
Is it just me or is Inota
actually good at badminton?
He's one of our strongest players.
And you wouldn't be wrong
in saying he's the best first-year.
I mean, he even beat Yusa the other day.
What? Wasn't Yusa wearing
resistance weights on his arms and legs?
That's how he trains.
[Ayame] Hmm. He's better than I expected.
Oh, Miss Manager, could you
grab shuttles from the staff room?
[groans]
[Taiki] Ever since
the practice match against Yusa,
I feel like I'm actually getting better.
Even after a second game,
my legs aren't tired.
And I don't lose my balance
on round-the-head shots.
I'm in good shape.
[inaudible]
But he still hasn't played
against me lately.
[Ayame] Inota!
Let's go to the staff room,
and pick up our shuttles.
I'm in the middle of taking a break.
Haven't you heard,
stopping suddenly is bad for you?
Ah, you're thinking of marathons.
Okay, and here we go.
[exclaims softly]
[Kazuma] Natsu! Here's your new face!
Matsuoka.
And Chii, spacing out, as usual.
I wasn't spacing out.
Oh, no, you totally were.
If you'd stayed like that,
you would've turned into a statue
and been hailed as Eimei's monument
to the beautiful basketball girl.
Where do you come up with this stuff?
[laughs]
[mischievous music playing]
[groans] Now that I'm manager,
it's, "Go here," "Do this."
Yeah, and I'm helping you, so ease up.
Before I started this gig,
I thought all I would be doing
was handing drinks to Yusa.
Oh. Hey, Ayame.
[Ayame] Hi there.
- You really did join a club, then.
- [Ayame] Impressive, right?
I don't think you'll last a week.
Okay, shut up.
Well, hang in there.
- Yo.
- Hey.
Seems like you know everybody.
That's one way to put it.
- They're both my exes.
- Both of them?
Yeah, the first guy was summer last year.
The second one who said hi to us,
he was beginning of this year, I think.
But they both ended on good terms,
so don't freak out.
She'd compete at an intergalactic level.
It must be nice to have
such a busy love life.
[sighs internally]
I'll never know what that's like.
It's not a numbers game, Inota.
My methodology is about dating anybody
who tells me they like me.
[exclaims softly]
Of course, I do have to shut down the guys
who aren't remotely my type.
[Taiki] Well, that's just casually rude.
Then where does Yusa fit in?
[Ayame] This has nothing to do with Yusa.
I mean...
To dumb it down for you,
if someone tells me they like me,
I definitely appreciate it.
Because if I don't like them then,
I might come to like them
if the two of us start dating.
And if that's the case,
why wouldn't I give it a try?
Even if there was someone else I liked
between trying to get their attention,
and coming around to somebody
who tells me that they like me,
the second option
seems like it would take less time.
[gasps]
So how about it, Inota?
Give dating Hina-bean a try!
[Taiki] You're right.
Getting confessed to
does make you think about them.
[gasps]
Huh? Huh?
We're back, guys.
Wait! Hold on!
Does this mean what I think it means?
[exclaims internally]
Things are looking good, Hina-bean!
We're going this year, too, huh?
The fall training camp!
I've heard it's really tough, though.
Yeah, I've heard it starts
with a run in the mountains.
We're gonna be staying
at such a nice place,
but we won't get to enjoy it at all.
And I think the hotel is run by someone
who went to Eimei.
Oh, for real?
That's why it's so cheap to stay,
even though we're such a huge group.
And have you heard this one yet?
The superstition about the campfire?
[Nagisa] Superstition?
So you know how there's always
a campfire on the last night?
The superstition is that,
if someone confesses their love there,
the fire will ignite in their hearts
and they'll fall for each other.
[Nagisa] What a cliche way to say it!
Last year, some seniors from badminton
and volleyball started dating.
It could be a coincidence.
It happened the year before, too!
Is there even anyone
you like in the first place?
Uh, what?
[adventurous music playing]
[Ayame] Two hours of a bumpy bus ride.
A hotel in the fresh mountain air.
Four days and three nights
of non-stop sports.
Badminton, basketball,
and gymnastics, all in one place.
Let the games begin.
[screams]
A spider!
- [Taiki] This trip may just kill her.
- [Ayame] No!
[Nishida] Don't slow down now!
Keep moving!
You got this, guys!
- [girl 2] Push! Come on!
- [pants, grunts]
[all grunting]
Don't pick up the pace out of nowhere!
[Coach Yuasa] Keep those legs moving!
Run until the end!
High knees on the way back!
Stay focused.
Last one! And now a burpee!
[adventurous music ends]
[whistle blows]
All right! Take a break.
[all panting, groaning]
Next up, we've got some footwork drills.
I'm dying.
We've done legs the entire morning.
And we have
a walling hell fest in the afternoon.
[boy] How is it that we drove
two whole hours to get here,
and yet we're looking at the same scenery?
Taiki, open the door.
We need to air this place out.
[Taiki] Yeah.
[boy] Basketball is running?
But they just ran with us
in the mountains!
Their gym is a bit further away,
so I guess they get the bonus
of having to run all the way there.
That sucks.
[Taiki gasps]
[boy] Why does rhythmic gymnastics
get to ride around in a bus?
It's 'cause our gym
is too far away! Ta-ta!
[boy] That's no fair!
[girl laughs]
It's a good thing our gym's
connected to the main building.
[boy] Hard pass on running.
Hey,
break's almost over!
Could you secretly make it
a little longer?
[Ayame] You obviously know
I can't do that.
Please have mercy on us, Manager!
[shuttlecock thudding]
[grunts]
[energetic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[munching aggressively]
Tea, anyone? Tea?
[shuttlecock thudding]
[grunts]
[energetic music ends]
- [thudding]
- [all panting]
TOTAL ANNIHILATION
- [Taiki] Haryu.
- Mm?
Wanna play a practice match with me?
I want to take stock of
what I need to work on.
- No.
- No? What is he, a child?
Haryu's the strongest player on the team,
so I want to go up against him
as much as I can.
[boy] Taiki, let's practice our shots!
Coming!
[Nishida] Good gracious!
The best bath in years.
Why are you talking
like an old man, Nishida?
He is right, though, it was a nice bath.
Listen, fellas.
The key to being a gentleman
is that, even if you think of girls
after a bath, you keep quiet.
You're not keeping quiet, are you?
I guess this means...
that other people
are going to see how Chinatsu looks
straight out of the bath, too.
[groans] That's been my secret privilege!
[Hina] Well, you look worn out.
[funky music playing]
Hina.
- I'll go on and head back.
- [Hina] Yeah.
You're wearing your hair down.
Yeah, it's 'cause I just blow-dried it.
Anyway, what's up?
It feels like forever since I've seen you.
Well, gosh, this has
really been a long day.
I'm beat, so I'll just go to bed
to be ready for tomorrow--
What are you saying?
The night has only just begun!
We're staying at a hotel.
Don't you wanna have some fun?
We gotta live it up!
And that's why I brought a game with me!
A game? I wanna play, too.
O-ho!
And you two there.
You're coming with us, too.
Why does this have to take place
in my room?
[Nishida] It's our room actually!
So, what're we playing?
[chuckles] Well, buckle up,
my dear friends.
It's called the King's Card Game!
- Nope, sounds lame.
- [Nagisa] Maybe we head out.
Hold up, hold up!
This game is way more fun
than you're giving it credit for. Come on.
So check this out. We have
these cards that act as the "king."
First, we all draw cards,
and whoever gets the servant card
becomes the one to get a decree.
Then, you draw a "royal decree" card,
and you have to do whatever it says.
GET FLICKED IN THE HEAD
[groans]
You know, this game
is starting to grow on me.
[groaning]
- I think we should give it a try.
- [Nishida laughs]
So everyone should take a card now.
[Kyo] Mm?
Kyo got it.
Then you draw your royal decree.
END EVERY SENTENCE WITH "MEOW"
Is this right, meow?
You're just gonna do what it says?
No questions asked?
[Kyo] In these games, you lose
if you get embarrassed, meow.
[Nishida] Next round, next round.
Who's the servant?
[Nagisa] Oh, it's Chinatsu!
[Taiki] Show me meow card!
Come on, meow card!
I have to get my hair done?
Oh, I've got this.
I have plenty of hair ties and stuff.
I've got a bunch
of hair stuff with me, too.
I'm gonna give you
the most incredible updo.
Prepare thyself, young Chinatsu.
[Chinatsu exclaims]
Wait! Oh, no, that's too...
[Nagisa] You!
Keep your hands on your knees!
[all chuckle]
[all laughing]
[Ayame] It's so adorable!
This is absolute gold.
Sending to Karen.
Nice job with the hair ties.
[Chinatsu] It's too embarrassing
if it's only me.
[laughing]
[Haryu] You can't let your guard down
playing this game.
I think watching is more fun than playing.
[Ayame] It would seem
that no one has noticed yet.
This game has a foolproof way to win!
There! The servant card...
is slightly dented on one side.
By taking notice of that small detail,
I'll be able to dominate this game.
Okie-dokie! I'll deal next round!
Yours. There.
For you.
And for you.
There.
And yours.
I got it.
[Ayame] Just as I planned.
STARE
During the last turn, I happened to catch
a glimpse of what the next card is.
STARE AT THE PERSON TO YOUR LEFT
And I thought, "This royal decree
has Inota's name on it!"
If he locks eyes with Hina-bean,
Inota will completely fall for her.
How bout I shuffle the cards?
- No! [groans]
- Sir, Taiki, here's your card.
Thanks, Nishida.
DECLARE YOUR LOVE TO YOUR LOVED ONE!
[gasps]
Oh, that's a great card!
This is starting to feel
like a slumber party!
[Taiki] Like my parents?
No, you fool, like someone you like-like.
And everybody here will keep your secret!
So! Out with it!
[mellow music playing]
[Taiki sighs]
[Taiki] The person I like is...
[closing theme song playing]